[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "And what was he physically doing to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "He was beating me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2008"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Was it Michael dying that motivated you to write this new book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "No, actually, Piers, I started writing this book in 2008, and I kept writing and kept writing and there was always something that was coming up that prevented me from actually putting it out.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Oh yes, everything changes, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "-- down it came.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Do you think he -- if he had lived, would he have ever had a chance to start over, Michael, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "That's -- that's what hurts me more than anything else because he could have started over.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "How has it been for you starting over?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "It was a very difficult task for me to start over because there were so many different interruptions when I was about to start over, and I would have to put everything on the back burner but I think that in everybody's life we go through different journeys and different paths and it doesn't always take us the way that we think it's going to take us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Yes, isn't she adorable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "She is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Jan would say that, wouldn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "And I thought --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "I mean, for all of you it's been very, very tough surviving that period, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PDT", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, I think what it is, Piers, is that when you grow up in the spotlight that everything is magnetized and everything is totally actually blown out of proportion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "DT", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Are you -- are you, oddly, because of the tragedy of Michael, as a family, are you oddly closer now than you've ever been do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "I would love to say, yes, we're closer than we've ever been but it's really interesting, Piers, because when -- when a loved one in your family and Michael was the first that we've lost.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "When you -- when you look back on it now, do you feel that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "When I look back on it now, it was fun times, it was wonderful times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "What are you getting at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Do you ever wish you hadn't gone into show business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "I didn't want to go into show business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Did you ever feel that in his relentless pursuit for you guys to be successful, that the relationship you had with him crossed the line, that it became abusive in any way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Did he hit you then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "But, as you grow older -- yes, I got one spanking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What did you call him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Joseph.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Do you still call him Joseph?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joseph"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "But if you called him dad, what would happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Do I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Exactly the same.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "How do you get on with him now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Do you think modern parents are a bit soft with their kids?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Well, what do you say when they speak back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I have pretty strong words with them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "And then do they learn from that or?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "No, I'm like you, I'm big on respect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Did your mother have a kind of slightly complicated relationship with the way your father treated you all or did she go along with it completely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "My mother was very quiet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Has he ever told you he loves you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Yes, all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "But only now, he didn't when you -- when you were younger, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "When we were younger -- no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joseph"]}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Do you remember the first time he said that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "ACKSON: I think I told him first, I said, \"Joseph, I love you very, very much, and you mean the world to me, I want you to know that.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Yes, and you must remember something which is very interesting is that I don't care who you are in life, everybody is looking for love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ",", "WRB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 309, "question": "So, he never really had love himself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "He never had love himself and so, how -- if you don't --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Did Michael ever say I love you to Joseph, do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Yes, he has, he did say that to him, yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael", "Joseph"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan", "Japan"]}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "I've got say -- I mean, he comes over as a complete monster in this book and it sort of prompts the question, when I talk to you now, you seem intelligent, you seem quite worldly-wise, how did you ever get together with a man like this in the first place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "It started with my having to go to Japan and my mother wasn't able to go with me, and she asked my father if he could go with me to Japan and my father wasn't able to go with me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "How did you feel when he did that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I couldn't understand why.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Why weren't they steaming in to save you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "My family was there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Did you love him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I walked out many, many times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "You never loved him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "But when did he first start being physically abusive to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "It was shortly after we were together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "And what was he physically doing to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "He was beating me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Was that the moment you broke free?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "No, it wasn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "How did Michael react when you did that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I don't know how he reacted at the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "How did you get out of his clutches?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I got rid of him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "When you got out, how did you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "I felt like there was freedom, but I was still nervous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Where were you when you heard that he died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "I was at home when I heard that he had passed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A."]}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Hear in Los Angeles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "Here at home in L.A., yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "How did you hear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "My father had kept calling and telling me to get over to his house, because I live about two or three minutes away from him, and to go over to his house.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Did you see Michael, after he passed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "It's like they had shed all the tears then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Yea it was closure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Do you still think that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Why are you so sure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "I will never ever think differently.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Who were going to murder him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "The people that were involved in his life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "Do you think we'll ever find out the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "I'm going to make sure we do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "Latoya, how are the kids doing now, Michael's children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "The kids are doing very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 752, "question": "What sort of job is she doing, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "She's doing a great job, fabulous job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "If you had the chance to talk to Michael again, what would you say to him, that you never had a chance to maybe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "I would tell him that I'm sorry that I wasn't there to help him to start over.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}]